squarebrothers.com 2011-05-15

# Your Privacy is Assured : We wont sell your email address to anyone

|  |  |   
---  
  
**Privacy Policy : **This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Square Brothers collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of our web site and hosting service. **Privacy :** Users’ privacy is very important to Square Brothers Square Brothers is committed to safeguarding the information Users entrust to Square Brothers This Web site is not directed at children under 13 years of age. **The Information We Collect :** Square Brothers may collect personally identifiable information from Users in a variety of ways, including through online forms for ordering products and services, and other instances where Users are invited to volunteer such information. Square Brothers may also collect information about how Users use our Web site, for example, by tracking the number of unique views received by the pages of the Web site or the domains from which Users originate. We may use "cookies" to track how Users use our Web site. A cookie is a piece of software that a Web server can store on the Users PC and use to identify the User should they visit the Web site again. While not all of the information that we collect from Users is personally identifiable, it may be associated with personally identifiable information that Users provide us through our Web site. **How We Use Information :** Square Brothers may use personally identifiable information collected through our Web site to contact Users regarding products and services offered by Square Brothers and its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners, and otherwise to enhance Users’ experience with Square Brothers and such affiliates, independent contractors and business partners. Square Brothers may also use information collected through our Web site for research regarding the effectiveness of the Web site and the marketing, advertising and sales efforts of Square Brothers, its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners. **Disclosure of Information :** Square Brothers may disclose information collected from Users to trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners who will use the information for the purposes outlined above. We may also disclose aggregate, anonymous data based on information collected from Users to investors and potential partners. Finally, we may transfer information collected from Users in connection with a sale of Square Brother's business. **Maintenance of Information :** Information about Users that is maintained on our systems is protected using industry standard security measures. However, we cannot guarantee that the information submitted to, maintained on, or transmitted from our systems will be completely secure. **Questions : **Users may direct questions concerning this Privacy Policy by email to  **support @ squarebrothers.com**  
  
  |  | 

| 

We are here to help you  
  
---  
  
We are extremely happy  to you 24 hrs  a day, 7 days a week and 365 days a year.  
  
** Call on +91.44.26205355 / 56  
                       9884600900**  
  
Need Help? Chat with Experts!  

|   
---  
      
|   
---  

** 1. ** Experience  \- 8 Years of dedicated experience to Shared Hosting, Linux Hosting, Windows Hosting, Reseller Hosting, Server Management ( Both Windows & Linux).  
  
**2\. 24 x 7 Support** \- We provide real 24x7 support via email, phone and live chat. Our support response times are in hours and in most cases within few minutes.  
  
**3\. Flexibility** \- As your knowledge and requirement grows we are here to handle it efficiently with ease. Hundreds of people have started with shared hosting then grown to Reseller Hosting then Virtual Dedicated Server and then Powerful Dedicated Servers. Whether you go with Windows Hosting or Linux Hosting no matter we have a dozen of Redhat Certified Engineers & well seasoned Windows System Admins around the clock.  
  
**4.Management** \- All our popular shared hosting plans are hosted on Linux servers which comes with Cpanel the #1 management software for customers to handle their hosting accounts. If you go with windows hosting it comes with Plesk the #1 management software for windows servers.  
  
**5.True Value** \- You will get the real value for your money without any hidden costs moreover in the past we were increasing the features of hosting packages without burning our customers pocket :)
